[Music]
that the innovation of the Year award
goes to
FWD on behalf of FWD Asia group a big
thank you for the Asia Insurance review
and the panel of judges
we are very honored to be recognized as
innovation of the year
I want to thank all my colleagues in
this room table 24
and especially Leo Hui the team for my
team who leads this project
we cannot do this alone
your passion your Insight and
collaboration make everything possible
we wouldn't be here tonight without you
customers are something we are in the
center something we are doing about
and we believe Insurance deserve
breakthrough and innovation
here with coffee program
embodies activity vision of changing the
way people feel about insurance
[Music]
it goes beyond Financial benefits
with digital delivery we also support
our customer will with human touch
once again thank you for your support
and recognition
looking forward to bring the FW CARE
program to the next stage thank you
[Music]